Music
Good morning.
I'll be performing at the halftime show today.
I'll be there.
Music
Music. Music. Music.
Yes, today's halftime show
Ladies and gentlemen, the rain-living people!
Welcome.
Pleased to meet you.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
First of all, I'm going to ask you to make your marks.
Now, you see how the center side looks?
This is the center.
If you want to participate, you can upload your comments.
Have a good time.
Okay, so Amandrash, let's see you perform in the show!
Best regards.
Well, let's continue to do our best as always. Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to it!
~~
I'll do my best.
This is my second First Time Award,
This is our second First Time Award,
I think we're going to hit it.
We're playing on five surfaces,
We will deliver one song and one performance,
Let's have fun collaborating with Iris.
I think there are a lot of people who don't have this,
Americans like and enjoy,
Please laugh.
Here are two people who are very happy.
Congratulations.
Let's keep up the good work.
America's New Yuu Synchronome!
Chaim!
Thank you for watching. Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching.
I'm in rush, let out, win it, roll
Count me in, let us out, win it, roll
I should have it all this life
Chasing a dream, carving, lurking in the sky, above the sky
Beyond the waves, waves, waves, waves, waves, waves, waves, waves, waves, waves, waves, waves, waves
Beyond the waves Beyond the waves Beyond the waves Beyond the waves Beyond the waves Beyond the waves Beyond the waves Beyond the waves Beyond the waves Beyond the waves Beyond the waves
I know I can feel it
I think I feel it
Oh oh oh oh na na Oh oh oh na na na
Let me fix it yeah yeah
Make a brand new world
Oh you like that yeah yeah
You know you like that oh yeah
Say you like that yeah yeah
Yeah!
You are my girl
Do what you like
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Say what you want
Yeah!
Do what you like
Everybody say it's all right
I'm ready to be my own girl
Who cares?
When New Year's night comes
I can't say I'm ready
I got my girl
Oh oh
-end-
I have lost me to the wind and the road
One, two, three, four
Baby baby baby
One, two, three, four.
ellas
catch up the pace catch up the pace
my Don't like it
baby
Don't like it baby
Yeah, Yeah!
Make a brand new world
Who you like that?
Yeah!
Oh yeah!
Who you like that?
Yeah!
Oh yeah!
You're what you like
Yeah, Yeah, Yeah!
You're what you want
You're what you like
Yeah, Yeah, Yeah!
Who you like that?
Thank you, Iris!
Thank you!
That's all for us, AmeFlash!
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Ameflash, and thank you, Iris.
Once again, please give a big round of applause!
Nice performance!
And now for the raffle draw!
We will be drawing 5 winners from the audience today.
We will be giving away a signed paper autographed by Ameflash!
To enter, simply send a message to the official Kawasaki Brave Thunders LINE account
Using the comment function, enter the word "AmeFlash" in katakana
AmeFlash" in katakana and send it to us.
Entries will be accepted until the end of half time.
Please wait for the present!
That's all for today's halftime show! That's all for today's halftime show.
Let's go!
Good day!
Thank you very much.
So, thank you very much for collaborating with us this time.
This time we collaborated together on our song "Alive",
Thank you again for dancing during the halftime show.
Do you have any comments on how you feel when you dance? Are there any songs that are easy to dance to?
Miss Mikan" is a cheerful song,
It is fun to dance to, and I think it is a song that the audience can enjoy as well.
When we were able to complete the show as audience members, we also enjoyed it,
It was so cool to see everyone dancing so energetically!
It was amazing.
I want to use it as our choreography.
Thank you very much.
We hope you will dance to our songs in the future.
We would like to add more rhythmical songs to our repertoire.
Thank you very much.
We would be very happy if you could have acancers dance with us again.
Thank you for watching.
I'm sure you were able to watch the game until the very end, and I'm sure we were able to make it more exciting, and we won.
Congratulations!
It was cool and fun, and even when there was only a minute left, the scores kept changing, so that was really fun too.
It was so exciting not knowing the result until the very end.
I used to watch Iris's Alive performance from the audience, but this time I was really excited to be in a row with her.
I'm sure it was very powerful for those who were watching.
It was also fun to collaborate with Iris and change the choreography of our last song, which was a little different from our usual choreography.
Do you want to do it again in the future?
I'd love to do it with a bigger group.
I'd like to do it.
I thought so, too.
I think this was a little bit of the point for Iris-san, too.
This is how you used Alive.
We didn't even know about it.
That made us very happy, and we're glad that it's spreading in places we don't know about.
I hope you will use our song "Ame no Furashi" somewhere in the future, even if it's a different song, in sports, or in other situations where you're not an idol.
I think it's spreading to all kinds of places.I think... it's spreading to all sorts of places.
I'm glad!
I think it's something that could be done at festivals and book dances, like Alive!
I think it's possible to do it especially for the festival.
It would be great if you could use it.
I hope they do it.
I hope it will spread.
Please use it!